Meet Andy Sachs. A million girls would kill to
have her job. She's not one of them.
The Devil Wears Prada is a drama, comedy film directed by David Frankel.
A young woman from the Midwest gets more than she bargained for when she moves to New York to become a writer and ends
up as the assistant to the tyrannical, larger-than-life editor-in-chief of a major fashion magazine.
Miranda Priestly, played by Meryl Streep.
Andy Sachs, played by Anne Hathaway.
Emily, played by Emily Blunt.
Nigel, played by Stanley Tucci.
Christian Thompson, played by Simon Baker.
Nate, played by Adrian Grenier.
The Devil Wears Prada 2 is an upcoming American comedy drama film directed by David Frankel from a screenplay by Aline
Brosh McKenna, based on the 2013 novel Revenge Wears Prada: The Devil Returns by Lauren Weisberger.
A sequel to The Devil Wears Prada (2006), Meryl Streep, Anne Hathaway, Emily Blunt, Stanley
Tucci, Tracie Thoms, and Tibor Feldman reprise their roles from the previous film.
The Devil Wears Prada 2 is scheduled to be released in the United
States by 20th Century Studios on May 1, 2026.
The film explores themes of new york city, journalist, paris,
france, based on novel or book, journalism.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.